questions = [
    {
        "question": "What types of particles exist within the nucleus of an atom?",
        "correctAnswer": "Protons and Neutrons",
        "answer0": "Electrons and Protons",
        "answer1": "Protons, Neutrons and Electrons",
        "answer2": "Neutrons and Electrons",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the relative charge of a proton?",
        "correctAnswer": "+1",
        "answer0": "+2",
        "answer1": "0",
        "answer2": "-1",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the relative charge of a neutron?",
        "correctAnswer": "0",
        "answer0": "+1",
        "answer1": "+2",
        "answer2": "-1",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the relative charge of an electron?",
        "correctAnswer": "0",
        "answer0": "-1",
        "answer1": "+1",
        "answer2": "-2",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the relative charge of an alpha particle?",
        "correctAnswer": "+2",
        "answer0": "-4",
        "answer1": "+4",
        "answer2": "-2",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the relative charge of a beta particle?",
        "correctAnswer": "-1",
        "answer0": "0",
        "answer1": "+1",
        "answer2": "-2",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the relative charge of gamma radiation?",
        "correctAnswer": "0",
        "answer0": "-1",
        "answer1": "+1",
        "answer2": "+2",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mass of a lithium atom?",
        "correctAnswer": "7",
        "answer0": "5",
        "answer1": "10",
        "answer2": "6",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the atomic number of a lithium atom?",
        "correctAnswer": "3",
        "answer0": "4",
        "answer1": "7",
        "answer2": "10",
    },
    {
        "question": "A radon atom has 86 protons and 136 neutrons. How many electrons does a radon atom have?",
        "correctAnswer": "86",
        "answer0": "50",
        "answer1": "222",
        "answer2": "136",
    },
    {
        "question": "A radon atom has 86 protons and 136 neutrons. How many particles are in the nucleus of a radon atom?",
        "correctAnswer": "222",
        "answer0": "50",
        "answer1": "136",
        "answer2": "86",
    }
]